In this concept, you'll be introduced to services
在这个概念中 您将被引入服务
within AWS that are based on servers or instances.
基于服务器或实例的 AWS 中
These services basically consist of
这些服务基本上包括
individual servers that have software installed by AWS for you,
具有 AWS 为您安装的软件的各个服务器
and are managed by AWS.
由 AWS管理
Having AWS run these servers as a service,
使 AWS 作为服务运行这些服务器
removes a lot of the configuration and optimization work from your plate.
从板中除去大量配置和优化工作
Further, AWS can use their knowledge of
此外  AWS 还可以使用它们的知识
their internal infrastructure to create
要创建的内部基础结构
the optimal environment for the service to run it.
服务的最佳运行环境
AWS has entire teams of experts operating these software applications,
AWS 拥有所有运营这些软件应用程序的专家团队
which allows you to spend your effort consuming these applications,
允许您花费精力消耗这些应用程序
not developing or maintaining them.
而不是发展或维持它们
How do we spot a server-based service?
我们如何发现基于服务器的服务?
Does a service run in your VPC?
是否在 VPC中运行服务 ?
Are you configuring a group of subnets for the service to use?
是否要配置一组子网以供服务使用 ?
These are good signs the service is server-based.
这些是服务基于服务器的良好标志
Are you providing a security group for the service?
您是否为服务提供安全组 ?
Security groups belong to a VPC,
安全组属于 VPC
and get placed on service instances.
并将其放置在服务实例上
If you're choosing an instance type of instance family,
如果您选择的实例类型为实例系列
very likely that this service is instance-based.
很可能是基于实例的服务
Is the service an AWS managed service for a preexisting application?
是否为预先存在的应用程序服务 AWS 受管服务 ?
Think, MySQL, Redis, Elasticsearch,
思考  MySQL  Redis  Elasticsearch
these are all applications that you could run anywhere.
这些都是可以在任何地方运行的应用程序
AWS simply serves these applications for you.
AWS 仅为您提供这些应用程序
These services run generally the same versions of software you can get elsewhere.
这些服务通常运行相同版本的软件 您可以到其他地方
They're just being deployed to servers that AWS is managing for you.
它们正被部署到 AWS 为您管理的服务器上
Some examples of server-based services in AWS,
AWS 中基于服务器的服务的一些示例
ElastiCache, a managed caching service,
ElastiCache  受管高速缓存服务
Elasticsearch, which is managed Elasticsearch, Document DB,
Elasticsearch 它是受管 Elasticsearch 文档 DB
AWS's managed MongoDB, and Elastic MapReduce,
AWS的受管 MongoDB 和 Elastic MapReduce
AWS's managed big data service.
AWS 管理的大数据服务
You might think these are just MySQL servers,
你可能认为这些只是 MySQL 服务器
why do I need to pay AWS to run them?
我为什么要付钱给 AWS
Two important points here.
这里有两个要点
One, AWS has teams of people who are
一  AWS 有团队
experts in each one of these services. You likely do not.
每一项服务的专家  你不可能
Two, RDS costs about the same as renting
二  RDS 与租用差不多
the equivalent size EC2 instance and running the database yourself.
等效大小 EC2 实例并自行运行数据库
But running a database yourself
但是自己运行数据库
entails all the overhead of system planning and maintenance.
包含系统规划和维护的所有开销
RDS takes care of all of that for you.
RDS 把所有这些都照顾到你
These services provide a lot of value for slight,
这些服务提供了很多细微的价值
if any additional cost.
如果有任何额外费用